

Profile

Last couple of years I spent on self-education and work as frontend web developer after my decision about career switch. My previous entire professional career has been associated with taking care about people problems, workflow management, teamwork and teaching other people in my specialty. This experience of work was a great school for building my soft skills. All these qualities I took with me into a web developer career.

I'm very fond of web development cause it makes me feel my ability of creating something new. This is a profession that holds the future and it provides great possibilities for my personal and professional growth. I'm sure that my love and ability to learn and gain new knowledge and new skills, my life experience and my soft skills will lead me through the path of becoming a successful web developer.

Employment History

Frontend Web Developer, Web Creation Studio, Donetsk, Ukraine

OCTOBER 2021 - JULY 2022

- Developed code (HTML, CSS, JavaScript) to convert design (built in Figma) into website (under supervision).
- Used React for front end development (created separate components that were later used in applications).
- Collaborated with web designers to design and improve websites
- Made changes in design of web products made by other people to meet clients' requirements

Frontend Web Developer (Intern), WebImpulse, Donetsk, Ukraine

JUNE 2021 - AUGUST 2021

- Developed code (HTML, CSS, JavaScript) to convert design (built in Figma) into website (under supervision).
- Used React for front end development (created separate components that were later used in applications).
- Assisted senior Front End Developer in developing of web applications and gained skills in aligning result with clients' requirements.
- Learned how senior Front End Developer debugged his code to improve website performance and user experience.

Deputy Dean of the Faculty of Dentistry, Donetsk National Medical University, Donetsk, Ukraine

NOVEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2019

- Created annual plan of educational work at the Faculty of Dentistry and monitored its implementation.
- Took part at control of educational progress of 1st-5th-year students of the Faculty of Dentistry.
- Took part at control of attendance of practical classes of 1st-5th-year students of the Faculty of Dentistry.
- Organized and controlled mentorship for the 1st-year students to ensure their successful adaptation in University.
- Took part in organization of cultural extracurricular activities in University.

Details

Ukraine (look for remote work or relocation) +380719017755 dr.volvakov@gmail.com

Links

<u>LinkedIn</u>

GitHub

Twitter

Skills

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

React

Bootstrap

Git

Languages

Ukrainian

Russian

English

German

Dentist, Principal Dentist, My Entepreneurship, Donetsk, Ukraine

- Provide therapeutic and prosthodontic dental care to patients.
- Fill medical documentation.
- Clinical workflow organization.
- Supervise the operation of the practice to ensure that patients receive high quality dental treatment.
- Supervise quality of infection control in the practice.
- Organization of supplies of medicines and consumables.
- · Personnel hiring.
- Interaction with public authorities (Ministry of Health, Ministry of Revenue and Fees, etc.)

Assistant of the Department of Prosthetic Dentistry, Donetsk National Medical University, Donetsk, Ukraine

FEBRUARY 2009 - JUNE 2022

- Held practical classes on prosthetic dentistry for students of Faculty of Dentistry and International Medical Faculty of University.
- Gave lectures on prosthetic dentistry for students of International Medical Faculty of University.
- Provided mentorship for students during their extracurricular dental practice.
- Created guides for students to master different topics of prosthetic dentistry.
- Took part in creation of 2 textbooks on prosthetic dentistry.
- Provided prosthodontic dental care to patients that addressed to Department.
- Performed scientific research.
- Published articles with results of research in scientific dental journals.

Dentist, Private dental practice Ltd., Donetsk, Ukraine

OCTOBER 2008 - DECEMBER 2013

- Provided therapeutic and prosthodontic dental care to patients.
- Filled medical documentation.

Dentist (Clinical Internship), Central City Clinical Hospital #1, Donetsk, Ukraine

AUGUST 2006 - AUGUST 2008

- Provided therapeutic, prosthodontic and surgical dental care (under supervision) to patients.
- Filled medical documentation.

Education

Bachelor (BSc), Donetsk State Medical University, Donetsk, Ukraine

SEPTEMBER 2001 - JUNE 2006

Graduated Bachelor program in the specialty "Dentistry" with High Honors

Master's Degree (MSc), Donetsk State Medical University, Donetsk

SEPTEMBER 2006 - JUNE 2008

Graduated Magistracy in the specialty "Dentistry" with High Honours

Bachelor (BSc), The International University of Finance, Donetsk, Ukraine

OCTOBER 2007 - OCTOBER 2009

Graduated Bachelor program in the specialty "Finance"

Courses

Code-Basics, HTML for beginners

2021

Modern JavaScript From The Beginning, Brad Traversy

2021

50 Projects In 50 Days - HTML, CSS & JavaScript, Brad Traversy

2021

ReactJS from Zero to Hero, Vladilen Minin

2021

ReactJS - Samurai Way 1.0, IT-Kamasutra

2021

React Crash Course for Beginners 2021, Academind

2021

React Front To Back 2022, Brad Traversy

2022

JavaScript / Front-end developer, Rolling Scopes School

2022